[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "I mean would you assume with your legal brain that he was making a point there?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "would", "you", "assume", "with", "your", "legal", "brain", "that", "he", "was", "making", "a", "point", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I think he might be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "might", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Anthony"]}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "If you were about to talk to him, Dan, what would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "about", "to", "talk", "to", "him", ",", "Dan", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I guess one of the things I'd want to know is the George Anthony factor, the father.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "one", "of", "the", "things", "I", "'d", "want", "to", "know", "is", "the", "George", "Anthony", "factor", ",", "the", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Jeff Ashton, I mean, were you going to retire anyway, or has this kind of put you off the justice system?", "question_tokens": ["Jeff", "Ashton", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "were", "you", "going", "to", "retire", "anyway", ",", "or", "has", "this", "kind", "of", "put", "you", "off", "the", "justice", "system", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "No, no, it was planned anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "it", "was", "planned", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff Ashton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What was your reaction when you realized it had gone the wrong way?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "realized", "it", "had", "gone", "the", "wrong", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, I think the reaction of all of us was we were pretty shocked, as everyone else was, but you know all of us have been doing this long enough to know that anytime you have a jury making a decision, you just never know what they're going to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "reaction", "of", "all", "of", "us", "was", "we", "were", "pretty", "shocked", ",", "as", "everyone", "else", "was", ",", "but", "you", "know", "all", "of", "us", "have", "been", "doing", "this", "long", "enough", "to", "know", "that", "anytime", "you", "have", "a", "jury", "making", "a", "decision", ",", "you", "just", "never", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I think if this jury, you know, came to the verdict they did based upon the belief in something that wasn't in evidence.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "if", "this", "jury", ",", "you", "know", ",", "came", "to", "the", "verdict", "they", "did", "based", "upon", "the", "belief", "in", "something", "that", "was", "n't", "in", "evidence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What is the more likely premise now that this is all over, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "more", "likely", "premise", "now", "that", "this", "is", "all", "over", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Would you concur with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "concur", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, I don't think that the sentence necessarily is a comment on how the judge felt about the more serious charges.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "the", "sentence", "necessarily", "is", "a", "comment", "on", "how", "the", "judge", "felt", "about", "the", "more", "serious", "charges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Was that the key problem here, that the forensic evidence just wasn't there for you to get a conviction?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "the", "key", "problem", "here", ",", "that", "the", "forensic", "evidence", "just", "was", "n't", "there", "for", "you", "to", "get", "a", "conviction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Well, you know, obviously, we thought the forensic evidence was there to establish her guilt of first-degree murder.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "obviously", ",", "we", "thought", "the", "forensic", "evidence", "was", "there", "to", "establish", "her", "guilt", "of", "first-degree", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "I mean, do you feel comfortable that someone who is a -- clearly a pathological liar, who was an appallingly negligent mother, if nothing else, clearly not, in my view, in any fit mental state, do you feel comfortable that somebody like that will be walking the streets of America in a few days' time?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "comfortable", "that", "someone", "who", "is", "a", "--", "clearly", "a", "pathological", "liar", ",", "who", "was", "an", "appallingly", "negligent", "mother", ",", "if", "nothing", "else", ",", "clearly", "not", ",", "in", "my", "view", ",", "in", "any", "fit", "mental", "state", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "comfortable", "that", "somebody", "like", "that", "will", "be", "walking", "the", "streets", "of", "America", "in", "a", "few", "days", "'", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, you know, we did what we could to prevent that, but the jury spoke and I believe the judge gave her the maximum sentence that he could.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "did", "what", "we", "could", "to", "prevent", "that", ",", "but", "the", "jury", "spoke", "and", "I", "believe", "the", "judge", "gave", "her", "the", "maximum", "sentence", "that", "he", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff Ashton"]}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What did you make of what he said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, I mean, first of all, I should tell you that most of the people who watched this case thought that Jeff Ashton did a very good job as a prosecutor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "should", "tell", "you", "that", "most", "of", "the", "people", "who", "watched", "this", "case", "thought", "that", "Jeff", "Ashton", "did", "a", "very", "good", "job", "as", "a", "prosecutor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "It was -- it was the most censorious sentence he could have imposed?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "it", "was", "the", "most", "censorious", "sentence", "he", "could", "have", "imposed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, Piers, I happen to agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "happen", "to", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Is that fair, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "fair", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I absolutely think it's fair.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "think", "it", "'s", "fair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Should they have charged on slightly lesser charges, do you think, or not?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "they", "have", "charged", "on", "slightly", "lesser", "charges", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "No, I don't believe they should.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "they", "should", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Do you think that that was what wend wrong here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "that", "was", "what", "wend", "wrong", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "WP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I do think there was a potential for overcharging.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "think", "there", "was", "a", "potential", "for", "overcharging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Let me ask you first, Stacey?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "first", ",", "Stacey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I believe she was guilty of murder.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "she", "was", "guilty", "of", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stacey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Robin?", "question_tokens": ["Robin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I don't necessarily agree that it's first-degree murder.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "necessarily", "agree", "that", "it", "'s", "first-degree", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Were you surprised by how quickly Casey Anthony's being set free?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "how", "quickly", "Casey", "Anthony", "'s", "being", "set", "free", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "No, not at all, given the good time laws and the way that most states work in releasing prisoners, I'm not surprised at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", ",", "given", "the", "good", "time", "laws", "and", "the", "way", "that", "most", "states", "work", "in", "releasing", "prisoners", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "surprised", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Well, will she have any restrictions on her when she walks through those gates out of prison?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "will", "she", "have", "any", "restrictions", "on", "her", "when", "she", "walks", "through", "those", "gates", "out", "of", "prison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "That was a surprising part of it for me.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "surprising", "part", "of", "it", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "What did you make of the events of the last 48 hours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "the", "events", "of", "the", "last", "48", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I can tell you that I'm aware of the fact that this young lady was, in effect, tried in the court of public opinion long before the actual trial took place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "I", "'m", "aware", "of", "the", "fact", "that", "this", "young", "lady", "was", ",", "in", "effect", ",", "tried", "in", "the", "court", "of", "public", "opinion", "long", "before", "the", "actual", "trial", "took", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What would you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Look, this is a perfect example, this case, of while you're innocent until proven guilty in a court of law, you're guilty until proven innocent in the media.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "this", "is", "a", "perfect", "example", ",", "this", "case", ",", "of", "while", "you", "'re", "innocent", "until", "proven", "guilty", "in", "a", "court", "of", "law", ",", "you", "'re", "guilty", "until", "proven", "innocent", "in", "the", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Would you agree?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I think it's a very complex family relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "complex", "family", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last three years"]}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Unless you are the person who knows exactly what's happened to her?", "question_tokens": ["Unless", "you", "are", "the", "person", "who", "knows", "exactly", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Well, all I can tell you is what all the arm chair quarterbacks have said over the last three years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "all", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "is", "what", "all", "the", "arm", "chair", "quarterbacks", "have", "said", "over", "the", "last", "three", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110707pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What does your gut tell you about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "your", "gut", "tell", "you", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I think my gut tells me what it's been telling me for the last 250 or so trials that I've covered.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "my", "gut", "tells", "me", "what", "it", "'s", "been", "telling", "me", "for", "the", "last", "250", "or", "so", "trials", "that", "I", "'ve", "covered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]